Oh, hey, Joey.
Mmm. Hey.
Listen, um, I need
to ask you something.
Okay, you know
how my stepdad's in prison?
Yeah.
Yeah, well,
um, listen, he was supposed
to get a weekend furlough
so he could come
to the wedding tomorrow,
but he just called and, well,
apparently, stabbing "Iceman"
in the exercise yard
just couldn't wait
until Monday, so...
So, he can't come?
No.
And so there's no one
to walk me down the aisle,
and, well, I would just really
love it if you would do it.
Seriously?
Yeah. You've, you know,
sort of been like a dad to me.
I mean, you've always,
you know, looked out for me
and shared your wisdom.
I am pretty wisdomous.
So, what do you say?
Are you kidding?
Phoebe, I would be honored.
Oh... thank you.
Ooh...
I hope...
I hope you know how much
you mean to me.
Listen. I hope...
I hope that you know...
I don't want you
to see your father cry.
Go to your room!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Oh, here.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let your dad get this.
Ah...
( phone rings )
Oh...
It's my wedding planner.
She's driving me crazy.
Hello.
Hey, okay, stop screaming.
Okay, so halibut.
All right, so salmon,
either way, I don't...
It doesn't matter to me!
Well, it matters to me!
Well...
I don't care,
so you pick.
Did you just hang up on me?
All right, look, I need you
at the rehearsal dinner
tonight at 1800 hours.
Uh-huh. Okay.
What time is that?
You don't know military time?
I must have been
in missile training
the day they taught that.
Just subtract 12.
Okay, so, 1,800
minus 12 is...
1,788...
Six o'clock!
Okay.
( phone rings )
Hold on. Yeah.
Geller here.
No, I said it has to be there
by 4:00. Good-bye.
God, how hard is it to make
an ice sculpture?
Ice sculpture?
That sounds really fancy.
I told you, I just
want a simple wedding.
Please. Honey, leave
the details to me.
Now, I want to make this day
as special for you as I can.
Now, okay, I
was thinking
that the harpist
should wear white.
Well, harpist?
My friend Marjorie
is playing the steel drums.
Oh, she backed out.
She did? Why?
I made her.
Steel drums don't really
say elegant wedding,
nor does Marjorie's
overwhelming scent.
Hey. She will shower
when Tibet is free.
Hey. You look great.
Hey. You, too.
I'm so glad we're
having this rehearsal dinner.
You know, I so rarely
get to practice my meals
before I eat them.
Okay, what did we say
was your one gift to us?
No stupid jokes.
But I thought that
was for the actual wedding.
Rehearse it.
Hi.
Thanks for coming,
you guys.
Oh, yeah. Oh.
I, uh, I was,
uh, I was going
for a handshake.
Is that why your hand
is pressed against my crotch?
That is why.
Yeah.
Rach?
Yeah?
Where's Emma?
Oh, Monica made me send her
to my mother's.
Apparently, babies
and weddings don't mix.
Are you still crying
about your damn baby?
Phoebes...
you got to keep
the line moving.
Remember, 20
seconds per person.
You see these clowns
all the time.
Hey, you're
Mike's parents, right?
Yes, we are.
Gosh, our little ones are
growing up fast, huh?
How's that?
You know, on the one hand,
you're happy for them,
but on the other hand,
it's hard to let go.
Who in God's name are you?
Hey, I'm not that fond
of you either, okay, buddy,
but I'm just trying
to be nice for the kids.
You know what
I just realized?
We have no idea
what we're doing
in the wedding tomorrow.
Yeah, I thought
we'd be groomsmen,
but wouldn't they
have asked us by now?
When did they ask you
to be a bridesmaid?
Uh, November.
I want to say
it's not looking good.
Hey, Phoebes?
Sorry?
You haven't told these guys
what they're doing
in the wedding yet.
Um, well, they're
not in the wedding.
What?
Well...
this is really awkward.
Oh, and I can leave.
I'm sorry, you guys,
but, you know,
Mike's got his brother
and his friends from school,
so, you know, you were...
If it helps,
you were next in line.
You just missed the cut.
Oh, man.
This is like figure skating team
all over again.
I mean, synchronized swimming.
I mean...
I mean, the balance beam.
Help me.
Football.
Thank you.
Oh, Phoebes. Spit that out.
That has pork in it.
Oh!
I thought the pot stickers
were supposed to be vegetarian.
Yeah. I changed them.
I sent you a fax about it.
I don't have a fax machine.
Huh. Well, then there are going
to be a few surprises.
I can't believe
we're going to be
the only people that
aren't in this wedding.
I know. I hate being
left out of things.
And it's a wedding.
It'll be weird
if I'm not in it.
Hey, guys. How's it going?
Fine.
We're just sitting here,
alone, doing nothing.
It's our rehearsal for tomorrow.
Yeah, look, about tomorrow,
I've got a question for you.
I just found out
that one of my groomsman
had an emergency
and can't make it.
What happened?
Who cares? And?
And I was wondering if, you
know, maybe one of you guys...
I'll do it.
Me, me!
You both want to do it?
There's only room for one.
Pick me. I look great in a tux
and I will not steal focus.
No. Mike, no, no.
You want to pick me.
I mean... watch.
Eh?!
You know, I really don't feel
very comfortable
making this decision.
You know,
Phoebe knows you better.
I'm going to let her choose.
Well, if Phoebe is choosing,
then say hello
to Mike's next groomsman.
Oh, I will.
But I will need a mirror...
as he is me.
Please.
You're going down.
You are going downer.
Is that what they say
on the figure skating team?
I wouldn't know,
I didn't make it.
So, you know I'm filling
in for Phoebe's stepdad
tomorrow, right?
Yeah, yeah. Thanks
for doing that.
Oh, hey, my pleasure.
So what are your intentions
with my Phoebe?
I intend to marry her.
Oh... a wiseacre.
So, I understand
you plan to support your wife
by playing the piano?
Isn't that kind of unstable?
No more so than acting.
Strike two.
You're right.
She probably will support me.
Hey, unless we move
in with you, Dad.
Strike three.
You only get one more, Mike.
So, what, uh,
what did you decide?
I decided to pee.
Mike didn't tell you?
You have to choose
one of us to be
in your wedding.
One of his groomsmen
fell out.
Oh, no, no. I can't choose
between you two.
I love you both so much.
Just not enough
to put us
in the original
wedding party.
Oh...
But I don't want to choose.
It's...
Oh, okay, wait. Rach!
Yeah?
Um, Listen, I have
a very special
bridesmaid task
for you to do.
Oh! Goodie! What is it?
Well, there's a spot open
for only one groomsman
and you have to choose
between Ross and Chandler.
So, good luck with that.
What? What? No, no.
I don't-- don't want to do that.
All right. I guess I have
to find a new bridesmaid.
I'll do it!
Okay, it's 2100 hours.
Time for your toasts.
Do I have a minute
to go to the bathroom?
You had a bathroom break
at 2030.
Pee on your own time, Mike!
Now... in regards
to the toast, okay,
you want to keep them short.
Nothing kills a rehearsal dinner
like long speeches.
Okay, you just get in,
do your thing and get out.
Is that what you
say to Chandler?
It's 2101
and I am not amused.
Okay, the bride and groom
have a few words
they'd like to say.
Okay. Hello, everyone.
And thank you all
for being here tonight.
So tomorrow's the big event.
And some of you might not know,
but Mike and I didn't get off
to the best start.
Um, yeah, my, um...
my friend Joey and I,
decided to fix each other up
with friends, so...
I-I...
Oh, okay. I, um...
I-I gave it a lot
of thought and I fixed him up
with my friend Mary Ellen,
who couldn't be here tonight
because...
It's not...
not important.
Well, she's in rehab.
Anyway, so okay, yeah.
So, Joey said that he was fixing
me up with his friend Mike,
only he didn't
have a friend Mike,
so he just brought,
uh, my Mike.
And, and...
( clears throat )
But despite, you know,
it got, it got good.
Okay, I want to take a moment
to mention my mother
who couldn't be here.
Oh, God.
And... and moment's over.
So, okay. Um...
Oh, no. Forget that.
I can forget that,
and, oh, this is funny...
But you need to know that to...
to get that, so...
Oh, well, okay, um...
I... okay...
There... Okay, Monica,
I can't do it like this!
This is my wedding, okay?
I don't want,
I don't want this.
Or this. Or this.
Okay?
I just wanted a simple wedding
where my fiancé
can go to the bathroom
anytime he wants!
You know what, you're done.
What?
You're fired!
Cheers.
Hey.
Happy wedding day!
Oh, happy my wedding day to you.
Okay, now, Joey, listen.
This is going to be
bridesmaid central,
all right?
We're going to have
hair and makeup going on
in the bathroom and,
uh, oh, I had to move
a couple things in the fridge
to make room for the corsages.
Oh, man.
I wouldn't have had breakfast
if I knew there was
going to be corsages.
Hi.
Um... about last night.
I know you're
under a lot of stress,
and, uh, well, even though
the things you said
hurt me a little bit...
Uh, my point is, uh,
well, I'm willing
to take my job back.
Oh, well, that's okay.
I think, I think you and I
will do much better
if you're just, you know,
here as a bridesmaid.
Oh.
Is that so?
Okay.
If that's really what
you want, then, here.
I give you the headset.
Well, I don't really want
to give you the headset.
Yeah, well, I guess
if you're taking over,
then you should probably
return these messages.
Oh, this is a lot.
Uh-huh.
But I-I'm sure you
can handle this.
I mean, I have won awards for
my organizational skills,
but I'm sure you'll do fine.
You've won awards?
Mm-hmm.
I printed them out
on my computer.
Hey.
Hi.
Where's Rach?
She's in her room. Why?
Oh, I have to talk to her
about this groomsman
situation, okay?
I'm not gonna watch
Chandler up there
while I'm sitting in the
seats like some chump.
( knocking )
( gasps )
My God, you're breathtaking.
What do you want?
You haven't,
by any chance, chosen
a groomsman yet, have you?
Oh, Ross,
come on, please.
Don't make this harder
than it already is.
I'm not. I'm making
it easier. Pick me.
Well, Chandler said that it's
really important to him, too.
Listen, listen.
Whoever you pick is going to
walk down the aisle with you.
Now, I promise, I won't say a
word, but if you pick Chandler,
he's going to be whispering
stupid jokes
in your ear the whole time.
Oh, you are
the lesser of two evils.
Yes!
Sven, I don't understand
what you're saying.
What is wrong with the flowers?
Lorkins?
What the hell are lorkins?
♪ I know. ♪
Hey.
Listen, Mike,
if you were Swedish
and you were saying
the word "lorkins,"
what flower would that be?
Orchids?
Right there.
That's why I'm marrying you.
I...
Hello, Michael.
Joseph.
May I have a word
with you, please?
This is... is great.
Have a seat.
Last night...
( Italian accent ):
I tried to welcome you
into my family.
Instead, you disrespect me.
I cannot allow this.
Are you rehearsing
for some really bad Mafia movie?
More back talk.
And yes, I may be
borrowing a few lines
from my recent
unsuccessful audition
for Family Honor 2:
This-a Time, It's-a Personal.
Joey, I kind of have
a lot to do today.
What do you,
what do you want?
I want you to
take this seriously.
Phoebe is very, very
important to me, okay?
And I want to make
sure that you
are going to
take care of her.
Well... Joe,
I love Phoebe.
She's the single most important
thing in my life.
I'd die before I'd let
anything happen to her.
That's what I
wanted to hear,
because she's family, okay?
And now you're gonna be family,
and there's nothing more
important in the whole world
than family.
That must have been
one lousy movie.
That was me!
Hi.
Hey. Can I
talk to you
about this
groomsman thing?
If you pick Ross, you know,
he'll walk you
down the aisle just fine,
but if you choose me,
you'll be getting some comedy.
Even so...
I think I'm going to pick Ross.
Let me tell you why
you need to pick me.
Okay.
( sighs )
See, when I was a kid,
you know, I was always
left out of everything,
you know,
and it really made me feel...
insecure, you know.
I was always picked last in gym,
even behind that big,
fat exchange student
who didn't even know
the rules to baseball.
I mean, this guy would strike
out and then run to third.
Anyway, if I'm the only one left
out of this wedding, I just know
that all those feelings are
going to come rushing back.
All right, fine, I pick you.
Y-Y-Yes!
Make groom for Chandler.
Oh, my.
No, we're gonna
do it my way.
Because your way is stupid.
All right, I gotta go.
I have another call, Reverend.
Hello.
I'm glad we had
this little talk.
Yes. Yeah,
and thanks for all the
wedding night advice.
That didn't make me
uncomfortable at all.
All right, and so,
I-I'll see everybody tonight.
Okay. Bye.
Uh, did you guys
know that there's
a giant ice sculpture
in the hall?
Oh, my God,
what's it doing here?
I guess it got sent
to the billing address
as opposed
to the shipping address.
Oh! What a pickle.
My God. Everything's
such a mess.
Why is this
happening to me?!
How bad do you want to stick
your tongue on that?
How's it going?
Good.
I'm just getting some coffee
so I'm alert for the wedding.
That's what I
was doing, too.
Well, uh...
you have fun tonight.
You, too.
Oh, I will.
Me, too.
Wait a minute.
I know why I'm
being such an ass.
Why are you?
I'm not supposed to tell you.
You told us both
we could be in the wedding?
Well...
In my defense...
you weren't supposed
to tell each other.
Rachel, only one
of us can do it.
You have to choose.
You and me together again.
Rach, Rach, knock-knock.
Who's there?
I'll tell you
at the wedding.
Hey, I forgot my scarf.
You know what?
I can't do this.
I don't know which one
of you guys to pick.
Oh, you haven't
picked yet?
Oh, good, 'cause
I had, I had an idea.
I thought
it would be fun
if the third groomsman
was my family dog, Chappy.
What? A dog? No.
Rachel gets to choose.
Wow, this is
a tough one.
I think I'm gonna have
to go with the dog.
All right, wait, wait. So,
what, what you're saying
is that-that the chef
is at the Hamilton Club,
but the food is not,
and the drinks are there,
but the bartender is not?
Are-are-are you
freaking kidding me?!
How's it going?
Help me.
What?
I want you
to be crazy bitch again.
Really?
Please.
You really
want me to come back?
More than I want
to get married.
Okay, people,
we are back in business!
We have missed you so much.
Okay. Go get your hair
and makeup done
and I'll take care
of everything.
Hey, what are
you guys gonna do?
About what?
The blizzard.
I just saw on the news.
It's like the worst
snowstorm in 20 years.
They already closed
all the bridges
and tunnels.
What? But...
( gasps ) But the band
and the photographer
are coming
all the way in from New Jersey.
I don't think they are.
Ha-ha. Looks like
you're not going
to be in the wedding either.
So sorry, Pheebs.
Well, the club
lost its power.
Yeah, according to the news,
most of the city did.
Since when
do you watch the news?
Uh, for your information,
since they hired
a very hot weather girl.
I can't believe you guys
aren't going to be able
to get married today.
I know.
RACHEL:
Well, you know, it's
so beautiful out there.
You always wanted
to get married outside.
Why don't you guys
just do it on the street?
What?
Well, look,
it's hardly snowing anymore.
I mean, you couldn't ask
for a more romantic setting.
This could be the simple wedding
you've always wanted.
What do you think?
I think I want to get
married to you today.
Me, too.
Monica, do you think
we could do it?
Affirmative.
Okay, let's get
these chairs out here.
Gunther,
hit the Christmas
lights.
Ah...
Okay, who left the ice sculpture
on the steam grate?!
Michael.
Hey, you made it.
Great. Chappy!
There you go.
Hi.
Mom, I know getting
married in the street
isn't something
you approve of...
No, it's lovely.
The lights
and the snow...
I could look at them
forever.
I crushed a pill and
put it in her drink.
( chuckling )
Come on, sweetheart.
You know, Chappy's
too small
to handle
all this snow.
Someone's going to
have to walk him
down the aisle.
So, technically, would this
person be in the wedding?
I guess.
BOTH:
I'll do it.
Wait, no, but,
Chandler, hello?
I mean, aren't
you, aren't you
scared of dogs?
I'm not scared.
I'll just take
little Chappy and...
He can sense my fear!
My throat is exposed!
Well, I guess I'm
in the wedding, then.
Ha, ha!
He stinks.
Level one alert!
I repeat,
level one!
This is not
a drill.
Okay, we've got
a situation.
The minister just called.
He's snowed in,
he can't make it.
Oh, no.
JOEY:
Oh, hey,
don't worry.
I'm still ordained
from your wedding.
Really?
Yeah.
You think I'd give up
being a minister
and start paying
to ride the subway?
Uh, ministers don't ride
the subway for free.
I had to read
the Bible pretty carefully,
but, yeah, we do.
Okay, if Joey
does the ceremony,
then we have
to find someone else
to walk Phoebe down the aisle.
I'll do it!
( laughs mockingly )
Ha, ha!
Okay, Mike and Joey,
get in position.
Chandler, come with me.
Okay, Joey's doing
the ceremony,
and Chandler's
giving you away.
Oh, okay.
Hi, New Dad.
So, you ready to do this?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, my God.
This is really
happening.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, Phoebe, I'm so
happy for you, honey.
Oh, thank you.
I love you.
Oh...
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, no, no hugs.
The dresses.
Oh, what the hell.
Oh, come on.
( moaning )
I love you guys.
Love you.
Okay, it's zero hour.
All teams execute
on my count.
Let's get this bad boy
on the road.
Is it okay that I want you
to wear that headset
in bed tonight?
Uh, I have you scheduled
for nudity at 2300 hours.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, Marjorie, hit it.
( steel drums playing
"Can't Help Falling In Love")
Geez, Ross,
you could have showered.
It's the dog.
Groomsmen, why are you
just standing there?
Where is your bridesmaid?
We've got a broken arrow.
Bridesmaid down.
Oh, it's me.
Ready?
Okay.
Wait. Oh, no. Wait.
Wow.
But aren't you
going to be cold?
I don't care.
I'll-I'll-I'll be my
"something blue."
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
( steel drum music continues)
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
Aren't you freezing?
Nuh-uh.
( music stops )
( clears throat )
Friends, family, dog...
...thank you all for being here
to witness this blessed event.
The cold has now spread
to my special place...
...so I'm going to do
the short version of this.
Phoebe and Mike
are perfect for each other,
and I know
I speak for everyone here
when I wish them
a lifetime of happiness.
Who has the rings?
Okay.
When I was growing up,
I didn't have
a normal mom and dad,
or a regular family
like everybody else.
And I always knew
that something was missing.
But now I'm standing here today,
knowing that I have everything
I'm ever going to need.
You are my family.
Phoebe, you are
so beautiful.
You're so kind,
you're so generous.
You're
so wonderfully weird.
Every day with you
is an adventure,
and I can't believe
how lucky I am,
and I can't wait to share
my life with you forever.
Oh, wait. Oh, I forgot.
And, um, I love you.
And you have nice eyes.
I love you, too.
Uh, Joey.
Yeah?
Chappy's heart rate
has slowed way down.
Oh, okay.
Uh, uh, Phoebe,
do you take this man
to be your husband?
I do.
( softly giggles )
Uh, Mike,
do you take this woman
to be your wife?
I do.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
( cheers and applause )
I got married!
But could someone get me a coat?
I'm frigging freezing.
Thank you.
( steel drums play recessional )
That really was an
incredible wedding.
It was, yeah.
I kind of don't
want it to end.
Hey, you want
to come in for a drink
and a bite of corsage?
I'd love to,
but it's 2300 hours,
and I'm about to have the most
organized sex anyone's ever had.
Nice-- oh, hey,
whatever happened to Ross?
I don't know,
maybe he hooked up
with that hot girl
he was talking to.
Come on, Chappy,
do your business.
Make!
I did not sign on for this.